Guide to the Veranus A. Moore Papers, 1836-1958
Moore, Veranus A. papers, 1836-1958
- Series III. Correspondence
  - Prescott, Samuel Cate, 1927-1931 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Ravenel, Mazyck, 1908-1915 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Reed, Walter, 1901, 1904 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Reichel, John, 1906-1924 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Reynolds, M. H. [Myron Herbert], 1906-1917 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Rider, Jessie, 1908-1927, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Rider, Lottie, 1890-1892 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Rider, Ora P., 1891-1928, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Roadhouse, C. L., 1909-1929 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Robbins, W.A. (Mexico, NY), 1886-1913 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Robinson, Aubrey, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Rochester Health Department, 1906-1919 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Rockefeller, John D., 1910 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Ross, Frank, 1897-1919 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Rotary Club [Ithaca, N.Y.], 1914-1929, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Russell, Ernest, 1897-1903, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Russell, Harry Luman, 1903-1914 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Russell, I.H., 1892 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Russell, James, 1907-1929 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Rutherford, J.G. [John Gunion], 1905-1918 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Ryder, H.R., 1908-1918 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Salmon, Daniel E. [ See also Government Agencies-U.S.-Dept of Agriculture-BAI], 1906-1915, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Sandhovel, Mary, 1890-1892 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Sessions, F. W., 1916-1919 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Shackleton, Horace and Mary: See Series VII. Family Papers
  - Shepard, Franklin G./Jamestown Veterinary Hospital, 1906-1912 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Sigma Xi, 1897-1927, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Smith, Theobald, 1887-1925 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Smith, Wing: See Holstein-Friesian Breeders Club of New York
  - Society of American Bacteriologists, 1900-1928, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Southern Tier Veterinary Medical Association, 1914-1925 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Stange, Charles H., 1911-1927 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - State Charities Aid Association, 1908-1929 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - State School of Agriculture and Domestic Science [Delhi, N.Y.], 1917-1922 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Steensland, H.S., 1906-1908 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Stewart, Sesco, 1906-1917 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Stevens, F.C., 1906-1908 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Stocking, W.E., 1908 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Stony Wold Sanitarium, 1906-1914 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Syracuse Bureau of Health, 1908-1916, 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Tarbell, George S., 1911-1922, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Taylor, J.H., 1898-1921 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Taylor, Walter J., 1906-1923 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Thatcher, Roscoe W., 1928-1930 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Todd, Leona, 1904-1910 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Tompkins County Lab: See Ithaca City Hospital
  - Tompkins County Medical Society, 1907-1929, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Treman, Charles E., 1906-1929 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Treman, R.H., 1893-1930 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Tropical Products Company, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Udall, Denny Hammond, 1906-1919 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - United States College of Veterinary Surgeons, 1908-1917 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - United States Live Stock Sanitary Association, 1910-1929, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Utica Normal and Industrial Institute, 1910, 1912, 1920 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Van Es, Leunis, 1909-1925 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Walker, Eva and Katie, 1891-1901 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Ward, Archibald R., 1901-1930 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Way, Cassius, 1906-1917 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Way, Cassius, 1819-1927, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Weigel, Oswald, 1899-1912 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Westbrook, F.F., 1898-1917 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Western New York Veterinary Medical Association, 1914-1925, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Wey, Hamilton, 1897-1899 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Wheeler, George W., 1912, 1919 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Whitall, Tatum & Co., 1906-1921 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - White, Andrew D., 1905-1916 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - White, David S. [ See also Government Agencies-United States-War Department/U.S. Army ], 1908-1927 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - White, G. Franklin, 1906-1919 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - White, Horace, 1902-1929 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - White, J. DuPratt, 1915-1929 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Wilder, Burton G., 1882-1911, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Williams, Anna W.: See New York City Department of Health.
  - Williams, Walter Wilkinson, 1906-1926, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Williams, Walter Wilkinson- Requests for Circulars, 1916-1917 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Williams, Walter Long, 1917-1920 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Willoughby, C.L., 1908-1920 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Wills, John Gordon, 1906-1930, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Winslow, C.E.A., 1906, 1911-1920 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - World's Dairy Congress Association, 1922-1923 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Young Men's Christian Association, 1887-1915 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Government Agencies
    - New York State
      - Agriculture and Markets, Department of, 1897-May 1907 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Agriculture and Markets, Department of, June-Dec.1907 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Agriculture and Markets, Department of, Jan.-June1908 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Agriculture and Markets, Department of, July-Dec. 1908 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Agriculture and Markets, Department of, Jan.-May 1909 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Agriculture and Markets, Department of, June-Dec.1909 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Agriculture and Markets, Department of, Jan.-June 1910 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Agriculture and Markets, Department of, July-Dec. 1910 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Agriculture and Markets, Department of, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Agriculture and Markets, Department of, 1912-1914 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Agriculture and Markets, Department of, 1915-1916 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Agriculture and Markets, Department of, 1917-1918 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Agriculture and Markets, Department of, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Agriculture and Markets, Department of, 1920-1922 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - Agriculture and Markets, Department of, 1923-1926 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Agriculture and Markets, Department of, 1927-1930, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - Agriculture and Markets, Department of - Miscellaneous Test Reports, ca. 1905-1910 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Civil Service Commission, 1907-1930, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Comptroller, 1914-1925 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Cooperative Extension, 1916-1930 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - Education, Department of, 1895, 1904-1916 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - Education, Department of, 1917-1929 (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - Health, Department of, 1904-May 1908 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Health, Department of, June 1908 - 1917 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Health, Department of, 1918-1921 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Health, Department of, 1922-1923 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Health, Department of, 1924-1927 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Health, Department of, 1928-1931, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Legislature and Executive Branch [ See also Brockway, A. L.; Fenner, Casper; Kellog, O. U.; Lowell, S. J.; Sessions, F. W.; White, Horace; and White, J. DuPratt ], 1906-1916 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Legislature and Executive Branch, 1917-1922 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Legislature and Executive Branch, 1923-1930, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Patriotic Agricultural Service Committee, 1917 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - State Agricultural Advisory Board, 1911-1915 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - State Hospitals, 1897-1926, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous, 1899-1927, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - United States
      - Agriculture, Department of - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1866-1906 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Agriculture, Department of - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1907-1909 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Agriculture, Department of - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1910-1913 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Agriculture, Department of - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1914-1916 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Agriculture, Department of - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1917-1919 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Agriculture, Department of - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1920-1929, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Agriculture, Department of - Miscellaneous, 1906-1930, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Civil Service, 1907-1908 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Federal Board for Vocational Education, 1919-1921 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Legislature, 1897-1926 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - Public Health and Marine Hospital Service, 1907-1910 (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - Public Health Service, 1915-1929 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - Veteran's Bureau, 1922-1925 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - War Department/U.S. Army [ See also Marshall, C.J. and Series V. Subject Files - United States Army Veterinary Corps.], 1908-1917 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - War Department/U.S. Army, 1918 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - War Department/U.S. Army, 1919 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - War Department/U.S. Army, 1920-1929 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - War Department/U.S. Army, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - White House Conference on Child Health and Protection, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - Miscellaneous, 1908-1922, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous Wedding Announcements and Invitations, 1888-1929, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous Invitations, 1890-1930, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous Greeting Cards, ca. 1880-1930 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Postcards, 1908-1915, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1874-1897 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, 1898-1901 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1902-1905 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, Jan.-June 1906 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, July-Dec. 1906 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, Jan.-Mar. 1907 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, Apr.-June 1907 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, July-Aug. 1907 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, Sep.-Oct. 1907 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, Nov.-Dec. 1907 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous, Jan. 1908 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous, Feb. 1908 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous, Mar. 1908 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous, Apr. 1908 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous, May 1908 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous, June 1908 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous, July 1908 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous, Aug. 1908 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous, Sep. 1908 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous, Oct. 1908 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous, Nov.-Dec. 1908 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, ca. 1908 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Jan.-Feb. 1909 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, Mar.-Apr. 1909 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, May-July 1909 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, Aug.-Oct. 1909 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, Nov-Dec. 1909, ca. 1909 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, Jan.-Mar. 1910 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, Apr.-June 1910 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, July-Oct. 1910 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, Nov.-Dec. 1910, ca. 1910 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, Jan-Apr. 1911 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous, May-Dec. 1911, ca. 1911 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous, Jan.-Sep.1912 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous, Oct.-Dec.1912, ca.1912 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous, Jan.-Aug. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous, Sep.-Dec. 1913, ca. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous, Jan.-Apr. 1914 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous, May-Sep. 1914 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous, Oct.-Dec. 1914, ca. 1914 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous, 1915 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous, Jan.-Apr. 1916 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous, May-Oct. 1916 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, Nov.-Dec. 1916 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Jan.-Mar. 1917 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, Apr.-May 1917 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, June-Sep. 1917 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, Oct.-Dec. 1917 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, Jan.-Mar. 1918 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, Apr.-May 1918 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, June-July 1918 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, Aug.-Sep 1918 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, Oct.-Nov. 1918 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, Dec. 1918 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous, Jan.-Mar. 1919 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous, Apr.-May 1919 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous, June 1919 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous, July-Aug. 1919 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous, Sep. 1919 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous, Oct. 1919 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous, Nov.-Dec. 1919 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous, Jan.-Feb. 1920 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous, Mar.-Apr 1920 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, May-June 1920 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, July-Aug. 1920 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, Sep. 1920 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, Oct. 1920 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, Nov. 1920 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, Dec. 1920 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, Jan. 1921 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, Feb. 1921 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, Mar. 1921 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, Apr. 1921 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, May-June 1921 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous, July-Aug. 1921 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous, Sep.-Oct. 1921 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous, Nov.-Dec. 1921 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous, Jan.-Mar. 1922 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous, Apr.-Aug. 1922 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous, Sep.-Dec. 1922 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous, Jan.-May 1923 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous, June-Dec. 1923 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous, Jan.-June 1924 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous, July-Dec.1924 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous, 1925 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1926 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Jan.-July 1927 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, Aug.-Dec. 1927 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, Jan.-June 1929 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, July-Dec. 1929 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous - fragments, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Series IV. Writings
  - Lists of Publications, ca. 1899-1926 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Reprint Request Log, ca. 1895 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Library of Congress Book Receipts, 1898-1925 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Reviews and Notices, 1898-1925 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Quotes for Writing, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Book Reviews by V.A.M., 1916, 1918 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - "The Accredited Herd Plan", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - "The Accredited Herd Plan for the Control of Bovine Tuberculosis", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - "The Aim of City Milk Control", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - "American Veterinary Education and Its Problems" (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - AVMA Welcome Address and Response (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - "Anaphylaxis and Antianaphylaxis: Synopsis of Besredka's Work" (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - "Anaphylaxis and its Relation to the Tuberculin Reaction" (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - "Anthrax", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - "Anthrax", March 23, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - "Anthrax" and "Glanders", 1930 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - "An Attempt to Eradicate Bovine Tuberculosis from Cattaraugus County", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - "B. Botulinus and Botulism" (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - "Bacillus Coli Communis", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Bacteriology, 1907 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - "Bacteriology in the War", June 1919 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Dr. Bang's Introduction, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Bovine Tuberculosis, Jan. 16, 1924 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - "Bovine Tuberculosis in New York", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Bovine Tuberculosis and Its Control - Illustrations, ca. 1913 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - "Bovine Tuberculosis and Its Control" (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - "Bovine Tuberculosis and Its Relation to the Community", Dec. 1923 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - "Bovine Tuberculosis Control", 1924 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - "Bovine Tuberculosis and the Methods for Its Control", Nov. 1908 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - "Citrated Blood for Transfusion", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - "Commercial Pasteurization," U.S. Public Health Service Bulletin, 1925 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - "Contagious Abortion in Cattle", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Contagious Disease Address, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - "Control of Bovine Tuberculosis", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - "Cooperation of the Milbank Memorial Fund in the Eradication of Bovine Tuberculosis from Cattaraugus County" (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Cornell University's Graduate School, ca. 1909 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - "Cornell's Contributions to Veterinary Medicine", March 1925 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - "The Developments of Organized Veterinary Education in the Last Ten Years", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - " Developments of Organized Veterinary Education in the Last Ten Years", 1923? (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - "Diseases of Animals Communicable to Man with Special Reference to those Transmitted through Milk", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - "Diseases of Cattle Communicable to Man through Milk", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - "Diseases Transmitted from Animals to Man," Introduction to book by Thomas G. Hull, 1929 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - "Eradication of Bovine Tuberculosis from Cattaraugus County", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - "Factors Involved un Tuberculosis Eradication and in Maintaining Sound Herds" (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - "Factors in the Control of Tuberculosis", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - "The Federal Meat Inspection Service", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - "Fighting for the Herd's Health: The Nature of Bovine Tuberculosis", 1923 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Flagella, ca. 1893 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - "Fourteen Tuberculosis Questions and Answers", 1927 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - "Fowl Plague, a New Chicken Disease, in America" (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - "Function of the Veterinary Profession", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Germ Theory of Disease, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - "Glanders" (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - "Greetings to the Veterinary Inspectors of the Bureau of Animal Industry" (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - "Growth of the New York State Veterinary College at Cornell University", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - "Health for Others Sake", Apr. 21,1904 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - "History of Medicine", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Hog Cholera, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - "Hog Cholera and Its Control" (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - "Hog Cholera: History and Distribution of Hog Cholera in America" (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Immunity, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - "The Importance of Disease Control in Poultry Husbandry" (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - "Importance of Sound Herds", 1916 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - "Importance of Tuberculous-Free Herds", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Individual Responsibility, 1913 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Infantile Paralysis, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Infectious Abortion, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - "Infectious Entero-Hepatitis in Turkeys", 1897 (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - Ithaca City Hospital, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - Ithaca Graduation, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - Ithaca High School Graduation, June 28, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 82)
  - Ithaca Night School Graduation, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 83)
  - "Keep the Milk Stream Pure: Veterinary Dairy Inspection", 1923 (Box 18, Folder 84)
  - Laboratory Directions for Beginners in Bacteriology
    - 4th edition edits, pp1-70, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 85)
    - 4th edition edits, pp 71-150, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 86)
  - "Dr. James Law", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 87)
  - "Limitations of Tuberculin in Detecting Tuberculous Infected Animals", July 1, 1915 (Box 18, Folder 88)
  - Malta Fever [fragment], n.d. (Box 18, Folder 89)
  - "Duncan McNab McEachran: An Appreciation", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 90)
  - "Duncan McEachran and the McGill Faculty of Comparative Medicine", Oct. 13, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 91)
  - "Meat Inspection", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 92)
  - "Meat Inspection Relative to Public Health", April 1925 (Box 18, Folder 93)
  - "The Microscope", May 9, 1893 (Box 18, Folder 94)
  - "Milk and Dairy Inspection" (Box 18, Folder 95)
  - Milk Disease, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 96)
  - Milk Disease, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 97)
  - "The Montreal Veterinary College", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 98)
  - "The Nature of Bovine Tuberculosis", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - "The Nature of Foot and Mouth Disease" (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - "Nelson's Looseleaf Medicine" articles on Anthrax, Glanders and Hog Cholera (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - New York State Department of Farms and Markets (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - "New York State Veterinary College at Cornell University", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - "New York State Veterinary College at Cornell University", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - New York State Veterinary Medical Society Welcome, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - "On the Flagella and their Value in the Systematic Classification of Bacteria", 1895 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - "The Original Faculty of the Veterinary College", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - "The Outlook for Veterinarians", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - "Pasteur and His Influence on Comparative Medicine" (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - "Pathogenic Fungi and Protozoa" (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - The Pathology and Differential Diagnosis of Infectious Diseases of Animals (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - "Preparation of Nutritive Agar", 1890 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - "The Prevention of Fowl Plague", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Principles of Microbiology
    - Chapter 1, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Chapters 2-4, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Chapters 5-6, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Chapter 7, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Chapters 8-9, misc., n.d. (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Appendices, ca. 1916 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - "Examination of Cultures", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - "The Cultivation of Anaerobic and Partial Tension Bacteria" (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - "Methods for the Isolation of Bacteria in Pure Culture", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - "Isolation and Cultivation of Bacteria" (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - "Inoculating Culture Media", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Key to Charts, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - "Progress in Veterinary Education", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - "Progress in Veterinary Education", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - "Progress in Veterinary Education and Service at Cornell University" (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Public Health, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - "Puerperal Sepsis", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - "The Purpose of Laboratory Work in Veterinary Colleges", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - "The Purpose and Requirements of Veterinary Dairy Inspection" (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - "The Purpose of Dairy and Meat Inspection" (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - "Purpose of Living", March 23, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - "Questions in Bacteriology", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - "Questions in General Pathology", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - "Rabies or Hydrophobia", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - "Rabies and Its Control (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - "The Relation of Bovine Tuberculosis to Clean Milk", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - "Relation of Comparative Pathology to Human Diseases", May 1924 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - "Relation of Dairy Products to Human Diseases" (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - "The Relation of the Veterinarian to the Swine Industry" (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - "Remarks on Matters of Interest to Veterinarians of the State", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - "Report of the Committee on Diseases" (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - "Report of the Committee on Intelligence and Education" (Box 19, Folder 47)